A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA802 FA802
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, 45 record storage cartons, 1 oversize box.
  - Student Service of America (SSA), Inc., circa 1941-1948
    - Dr. Conn's folder. Mar 31, 1947 [sic-Correspondence, memoranda, pamphlets, ca 1946-47] (Box 7, Folder 16-17)
    - SSA rec from Dr. Cohn, 1947 March 24 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Contributions, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Contributions returned, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - SSA Inc. Irene Crosby [Petty cash accounts; c.v. of I. Crosby] (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Miss Crosby [Correspondence, minutes, reports, notes, programs; includes material on 20th annual conference of ISS held in Cambridge, England], circa 1946-1949 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - D (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Davis, Herbert (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Didier, Maurice (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Doerr, Wallace F. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - de Blonay, André (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - E-F (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Eagleton, Clyde (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Fackenthal, Frank D. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Ferenczi, Edmond (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Finletter, Thomas K. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Fisher, Edgar J. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Frykholm, Yngve (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Field Foundation (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - G-H (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Gideonse, Harry D. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Gotlieb, Howard B. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Gowen, Mimi (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Horton, Mrs. Douglas (Mildred) (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Income tax (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - J-K-L (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Josephs, Devereux C. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Koretsky, Cecelia (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Kotschnig, Walter M. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Klein, George P. See income tax file (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Lash, Joseph P. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - M (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Marshall, John MacAdam, Audrey (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - McClumpha, Margaret (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Directors and Members of the United States Committee of International Student Service (SSA, Inc.), 1946 March 2 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Agenda - Annual meeting, 1946 March 19 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - [Meeting at Hunter College], 1946 November 13 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Memo re change of name (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - N-O (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Nason, John W. (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Netherlands Committee News Sheet (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Oram, Harold L. (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Publicity (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - R (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Randolph, Bessie C. (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Membership - Invitations (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Invitations - Bd. of Directors (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - [Memorandum: "I.S.S. faces the crisis of the post-war university, " nd, multiple copies] (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Asia Institute: correspondence, memoranda, manuscripts, minutes, budgets, printed materials, circa 1940-1952
    - [Miscellaneous loose papers: New York City Cancer Comm. certificate of appreciation to Cohn as member of Asia Institute], 1949 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Affidavit and inventory of Asia Institute, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - United Asia Vol. 1 No. 3 (October-November (1948?) re Asia Institute pp. 282-3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - A (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Altschul, Frank (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Armstrong, Donald (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Asia Magazine (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Announcements, circa 1941-1951 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - Asiatic Studies, School of (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - B (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Barlow, Samuel L.M. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Beck, Lawrence T. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Bliss, General Robert Wood [Bryson, Lyman] (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Broadcast: "The Asia Institute. A Broadcast by the State Department beamed to Eastern Asia", 1947 January 31 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - By-laws (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Bulletin. [Reprint from The Art Bulletin], 1947 March (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Budget (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Accountant's reports (duplicate copies), 1949 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - C (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Chase, W. Howard (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Cohn, Dr. [Program and drafts of Cohn speech on "The role of independent scientific societies in intellectual progress, " at 7 Dec 1947 convocation; plus revision, 13 Sep 1948 with recommendations for status of Asia Institute as graduate school] (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - [Cohn, A.E. re appointments held at Asia Institute] (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Council, School of Asiatic Studies; Bryson, Lyman (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Courses (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
    - Directors, Board of [Meetings] (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Duggan, Stephen C. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - E (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Erdmann, Mrs. William (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes [see also folder 34 below] (Box 8, Folder 22-23)
    - Finance Committee Memo. Dr. Conn's report, 1946 February 23 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - F-M (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Fribourg, Arthur H. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Grimm, Peter (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Jayne, Horace (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Jewish Culture, Institute for the study of (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Kent, Lucy E. (Executive Secretary) (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Lee, Orient (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Membership Committee (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Mitchel, Samuel Latham (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda, 1950 March (Box 8, Folder 26)
      [Includes drafts of Cohn memo].
    - Minutes, Board of Trustees (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - 1945 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - 1946 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - 1947 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - 1948 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - 1949 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - 1950 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - 1951 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Executive Committee, Board of Trustees, 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - N (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Newsom, Carroll V. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Nordlinger, Riegelman and Benetar (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Norgord, Dagmar (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - News Letter, 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - O-P (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Oram, Harold L. (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Pool, Mrs. David de Sola (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Occasional Papers No. 2 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      [Speech by Rexford A. Stead].
    - Pope, Arthur Upham
      - 1940-1945 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - 1946 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - 1947 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - 1948 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - 1949 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - 1950 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Assorted subject files
    - Adams, Walter, circa 1933-1939 (Box 9)
    - Biele, Harry D., circa 1941-1944 (Box 9)
    - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, circa 1928-1935 (Box 9)
    - Institute for Psychoanalysis, circa 1932-1944 (Box 9)
    - Books, pamphlets, photostats [Orders], circa 1936-1950 (Box 9)
    - Reprints on heart disease by Cohn and others, circa 1927-1945 (Box 9)
    - Mss of essay on blood, circa 1952 (Box 9)
    - "Introductions to medical journals" [with photostats and translations of 18th-19th-20th c. material], circa 1926-1927 (Box 9)
    - Adams, Walter [General Secretary, Academic Assistance Council; name changed in 1927 to The Society for the Protection of Science and Learning]
      - [Reports and summaries], circa 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - [Correspondence files: rearranged by year; some of this material was apparently photocopied by R. Sternfeld for a researcher - the original locations are not known]
        - 1934 (Box 9, Folder 2)
        - 1935 (Box 9, Folder 3)
        - 1936 (Box 9, Folder 4)
        - 1937 (Box 9, Folder 5)
        - 1938 (Box 9, Folder 6)
        - 1939 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Biele, Harry D. [Secretary, National Committee for Resettlement of Foreign Physicians] (Box 9)
      Reports and memoranda.
      - 1941 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - 1944 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine (Box 9)
      [Correspondence and mss].
      - 1928 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - 1929 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - 1930-1933 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - [Drafts by Cohn of Committee report on improvement of meetings of NY section, Soc. Exp. Biol. Med., undated] (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Institute for Psychoanalysis [Chicago] (Box 9)
      - [Gen. correspondence, Alfred K. Stern], 1932 January-March (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - 1932 April (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - 1932 May-November (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - 1933-1935 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Alexander, Franz, 1932-1935 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Alexander, Franz; Grunsfeld, Mary-Jane, circa 1940-1944 (Box 9, Folder 20)
        [Includes material re publication of Cohn essay, "Psychoanalysis in Medicine"].
      - Freud, Professor. [Copies of letter, from Cohn/Freud], 1932 September 28 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Pamphlets, 1932 October (Box 9, Folder 22)
        [Institute for Psychoanalysis 2 copies (with markings for revisions) of The Institute for Advanced Study. Organization and Purpose].
    - Books, Pamphlets, Photostats [Orders] (Box 9)
      - Drafts. Lewis, Macmillan, etc., 1943-1945 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - [Correspondence, book reviews, newspaper clippings]
        - 1940-1943 (Box 9, Folder 24)
        - 1944 (Box 9, Folder 25)
        - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 26)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 27)
        - 1948-1950 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Fifth Avenue bank drafts, circa 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Reprints (Box 9, Folder 30)
      [From unlabeled envelope: assorted reprints re heart disease by Cohn and others, ca 1927-45].
    - [From black 3-ring binder: draft typescripts of non-technical essay on blood, ca 1952], circa 1952 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - [From "expanding wallet" file labeled "Introductions to Medical Journals" 18-19-20 c] (Box 9)
      - untitled (Box 9, Folder 32)
        [Correspondence, mss, newspaper clippings, bibliographies re history of publication of introductions for new medical journals, ca 1926-27; probably in connection with starting of The Journal of Clinical Investigation (Vol. 1 1924 - see introduction by Cohn.) This file includes 23-p typescript of untitled, undated, historical essay].
      - untitled (Box 9, Folder 33-34)
        [Translations—includes duplicates].
      - untitled (Box 9, Folder 35)
        [Photostats of originals].
      - "American" "English/Scotch" "French" "German" by journal, 5 × 8 typed index cards (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Sydenham Hospital, (a few earlier/items & later) Correspondence and subject files, circa 1947-1948
    - Brochure Comm., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Conference Comm., 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Morsell, John, 1947-1951 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Institute of Community Relations, circa 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors (Box 10)
      - [Notices of meeting], 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Plan by AEC, 1947 February 17 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Minority Report, 1948 February 25 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Resignation, Fund Raising [AEC], 1948 February 22 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - 1947 March 17 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - 1947 April 21 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Bd. Dirs. and Committees (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - 1947 October 27 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - 1948 January 13 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - 1948 February 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - 1948 March 11 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - 1948 March 11-22 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - 1948 April 22 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - 1948 May 26 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - 1948 June 23 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Executive Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Fund Raising, circa 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Library Committee, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Committee of the Medical Board, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Nominating Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Reorg. Committee 17, 1947 March 13 1947 February 26 1947 March (?) (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Steering Comm., 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Women's Division, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Cornely, Paul B. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Cotton, Thomas L. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Cowles, Gardner (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Dewey, Thos E. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Dingle, Alan M. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Davis, William H. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Dean, Abner (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Diamond, Joseph (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Dingle, Alan L. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Duggan, Stephen J. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Dowden, Ed (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Duggan, Stephen (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Editor, To the (not yet used) (sic), 1948 June (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Employees (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Eberstadt, Ferdinand (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Erdmann, Mrs. William (Julie) (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Erdmann, Martin (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Erskine, John (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Emergency Room and Out Patient Department, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Farrell, Mrs. W.E. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Field, Marshall (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Fields, Allen D. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Fleming, Henry Craig (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Floor plans. Census of beds (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Fremont-Smith, Frank (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Foundations (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Friedman, Sigmund L. (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - untitled (Box 10, Folder 29A)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Closed.
    - Fund raising (Box 10, Folder 30-31)
    - Gill, Dorothy G. (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Ginsler, A.M. (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Garrison, Lloyd (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Gelberg, Ruth (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Gilbert, Charles K. (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Ginzler, Arthur M. (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Greenberg, B. (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Godoff, Elliott (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Goldsmith, Harry (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Granger, Lester B (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Gregg, Alan (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Gutman, Mrs. Monroe C. (Edna) (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Greater New York Fund (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Hinenburg, M. (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Heiman, Jacob (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Henry, Leland (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Hirsh, Mrs. Elizabeth S. (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Hirst, Donald (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Hospital Council of Greater NY (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Howes, Edward L. (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Hyanis, Geoffrey Trust Fund (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Hudson, George (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Hughes, Charles E. Jr (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Hyam, Margot and Leslie (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - International Business Machines Corporation (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Interns and residents (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Industry leaders (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Isaacs, Reginald R. (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Jarcho, Julius (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Johnson, Charles S. (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Jackson, William Harding (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Jacobi, Lester (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Johnson, Mordecai (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Kaas, Josephine (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Kaempffert, Waldemar (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Kastor, Mrs. Hugo (Marion E.) (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Kogel, Marcus (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Kilpatrick, William H (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Kogel, Marcus D. (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Korshin, Nathan (Box 10)
      - General (Box 10, Folder 41-43)
      - Korshin resignation, 1948 February 25 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Contract (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Korshin-AEC report, 1948 January 6 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Procedures (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Lambert, R.A. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Larsen, Roy E. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lambert, Robert A. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - L'Hommedren, B. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lehman, Herbert H. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lenke, Mark (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lester, Raymond A. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Levey, Stanley (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lewis, John P. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Liebman, Joshua (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lilienthal, David (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lescaze, William [architect] (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Lord, William G. (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Lothrop, Donald G. (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Louis, Joe (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Luncheon, 23 October, 6, 25 November, 23 December (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - [Letter file: re SI pamphlet. Many copies in lieu of originals] (Box 10)
      - Bayne-Jones, S. (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Beard, Charles (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Blumgart, Herrman L. (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Boas, Ernst P. (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Cabot, Thomas D. (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Cane, Melville (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Cohen, Charles (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Duggan, Stephen (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Farrell, Mrs. W. Elliston (Emily C.) (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Fishbein, Morris (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Greenberg, Benjamin B. (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Hughes, Charles E. Jr. (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Hyam, Margot (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Jacobi, Lester (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Kashins, Clare Linsker (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Kirps, Maurice (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Lemann, Monte M. (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Lerner, Max (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Mackenzie, Richard (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Newman, James R. (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Neaman, Pearson E. (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Oppenheimer, Harry C. (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Pincoffs, Maurice C. (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Pratt, George (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Prince, Mrs. Leo (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Proskauer, Richard (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Richards, Augustus (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Steele, Katherine (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Swope, Herbert Bayard (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Swope, Gerard (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Taschman, Max (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Taylor, Harold (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Waddell, Mrs. Chauncey L. (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Sydenham Hospital, circa 1947-1948
    - [Duplicated items: Pages from printed pamphlet on meeting, apparently of/by Comm. on Chronic Illness of the Welfare Council of NYC, with reference to AEC. Mimeographs re Sydenham Hospital, Sydenham Institution] (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - [Holograph notes] (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - American Med. Assn. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Adair, Frank B. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Albert, Felix (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Addis, Thomas (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Angell, Ernest (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Angell, Roger (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Arnall, Gov Ellis G. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Asapansa-Johnson, C. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Astor, Mrs. Vincent (Minnie) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Astor, Vincent (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Austin, Augustine A. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Anonymous (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Announcements - dinners, luncheons (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Applicants (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Beard, C. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bernays, E.L. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Beckwith, Ellen (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Benlane, Mr. Berle, Bishop Beatrice (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Beth Israel Hospital [Rules and regulations], 1940 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bluestone, E.M. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Blaine, James G. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Blumgart, Herrman L. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bousfield, Col. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Boas, Edwin C. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bousfield, M.O. [includes 1945 history reprint] (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Brochure (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - [Brewster? ], Lyman (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Baldwin, William (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Budgets (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Cabot, Thomas D. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Calkins, Robert D. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Cantor, Eddie (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Chamberlain, Joseph P. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Chapman,. Stanley H. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Chase, Josephine (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Clancy, Mary Ellen (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Clark, Dean A. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Clayburgh, Alma (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Cohen, Charles (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Contributions (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Cohn, Peter [AEC relative] (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Cobb, Montague (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Collier, Louis W. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Cowles, Russell (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Campaign office (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Mausley (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Mason, M (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Mackenzie, R. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Martin, Marguerite L (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - McGoldrick, Joseph (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - McEwen, Currier (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Meyers, Harold C. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Merton, Robert K. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Meek, Frederick M. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Merck, George W. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Merton, Robert K. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Meyer, Mrs. Eugene [letter to Felix Frankfurter] (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Merz, Charles (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Morchand, Charles C. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Murphy, Gardner (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Murray, Florence (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Murray, H.A. (Box 11, Folder 15)
      [2-p ms: "Training Program for Psychiatrists" See also "Psychiatry" folder, no. 29, below].
    - Murray, Peter Marshall (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Murrow, Mrs. Edward R. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Murrow, Edward R. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Neaman, Mr. and Mrs. Pearson E. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Meetings and conferences (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Notes on. meetings (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 11, Folder 17-20)
    - News photos, 1948 February (Box 11, Folder 21)
      [with Joe Louis, Mayor Wm. O'Dwyer, AEC and others].
    - Oppenheimer, Harry C. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Syd. Hosp. Letter to Editors, 1948 November (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Resignation, various letters, 1948 August (Box 11, Folder 23)
      [Includes letters to Cohn].
    - Resignation [Clippings and correspondence] (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Odde, L.A. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Oram, H.L. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Orton, D. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - O'Dwyer, William (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Oxnam, G. Bromley (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Oram, Harold L. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Pediatrics (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Pew Foundation (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Pamphlet (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Parker, I. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Packard, Arthur W. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Paley, William S. Foundation (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Palmer, Dwight R.G. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Palmer, W.W. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Parsons, Geoffrey (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Pfeiffer, John (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Paley, Dorothy [Mrs. William S.] (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Protzman, L. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Poletti, Charles (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Pratt, Mrs. and Mr. Eliot (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Pratt, George (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Prince, Leo M. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Proskauer, Joseph M. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Provident Hospital Chicago (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Psychiatry/Neuropsychiatry (Box 11, Folder 29)
      [Correspondence, notes, clippings].
    - Reiss, H.L. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Resignation (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Reid, Mrs. Ogden (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Rhind, Flora M. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Rosensteil, L. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Roginsky, David N. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Rosenthal, Morris (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Rothbard, Dr. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Rubin, Samuel (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Releases, Press (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Sydenham Hospital/Institution Pamphlet, fund-raising, correspondence S-W, constitution and by-laws, circa 1947-1948
    - [Pages from 3-ring binder] (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - [Galley, page proofs for pamphlet] (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Statement re pamphlet "Sydenham Institution" (not yet used?) (sic), 1948 June (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - [Miscellaneous papers] (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The Struggle for a Voluntary Hospital in Harlem, Goode A. Harney, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 5)